italist.com 2019-04-03

# italist | Read our privacy policy

italist Inc. ("italist") is committed to protecting your privacy. At italist, we want you to have an enjoyable shopping experience. And while it is necessary for us to collect certain personal information, we respect and protect your right to privacy as set forth in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies to our websites (including italist.com), any mobile applications and related services (collectively, the "Services"). This Privacy Policy does not apply to other websites to which we link. You agree that your use of the Services signifies that you have read and consent to the collection, use and sharing of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, you should not use the Services.

## INFORMATION COLLECTED

User Provided Information

Registration with us is mandatory in order to place orders and fully use the Services. During the registration process (whether on our website or through downloading the mobile application), we collect personal information such as your name, email address or social media username. Once you register, you have opted in to receive electronic communications from us.

We also collect personal information when you choose to use certain other aspects of the Services, such as making purchases; subscribing to our newsletter; electing to receive text messages about upcoming boutiques, promotions or events; or if you provide it in response to surveys, contests, sweepstakes or other requests. When you choose to use these additional features, we may require you to provide additional personal information such as your phone number, billing and shipping addresses and credit card information, and we may request additional personal information such as your shopping preferences and demographics.

We may collect other information that you submit to us or that you have consented to permit us to collect or third parties to share with us from time to time.

Automatically Collected Information

In addition, we automatically gather certain information about your use of the Services, such as your IP address, operating system, browser type and a date/stamp time for your visit. If you use our mobile applications, this may include information such as the GPS data (i.e., geolocation data) and device information for the hand-held mobile device on which the mobile application is installed. We may also access your calendar to enable us to create and modify events on your behalf. We may also collect other information that you have consented to permit your mobile phone or application to share with us from time to time.

We may also gather information about how you interact with the Services, such as how frequently certain areas of our website or mobile application are visited, what products are reviewed and selected, order history, shipping program status, and other site navigation data and patterns. This information helps us to understand your interests and which aspects of our Services you find interesting.

Involvement of Others in Data Collection

We may work with third parties to collect and analyze the information as described above and for other purposes described below.

If you access our Services through other websites on which we have "stores," we will collect and analyze the information described above that is obtained through your interaction with that website. We may add this information to the information we have already collected from you via other aspects of the Service. You are also subject to such "store's" terms of use and privacy policy in connection with these Services.

If you access our Services with your login credentials from a social networking site (e.g., Facebook or Twitter) or if you otherwise agree to associate your italist account with a social networking account (e.g., Instagram or Pinterest), we may receive personal information about you from such social networking site, in accordance with the terms of use and privacy policy of the social networking site. For example, Facebook may share with us your friend list, birthday, information about the interests of you or your friends or other personal information, in order to help us establish your account, tailor the Services to you and find other current or potential Service users that you know. We may add this information to the information we have already collected from you via other aspects of the Service. You are also subject to the social networking site's terms of use and privacy policy. We use the OAuth (open authorization) protocol to enable us to access this information without collecting your password when you agree to allow another application to access your account information.

Further, we may obtain information from others (including social media networks, advertising service providers and networks) that does not identify you personally or, if you have given that service or us permission to do so, information that identifies you personally. This information may be combined with information you have provided to us or that we or others have collected about you, so that we may maximize the benefit you receive from the Services and deliver advertising targeted to your specific interests on our websites and mobile applications and when you use other websites or mobile applications. Information about you also may be aggregated with other subscriber information for the purposes identified above.

We and our vendors may use technology such as cookies and web beacons in connection with these activities to identify you when you are online, and to collect information about your online activities, such as the type of browser you use, the websites you visit and the content and advertising that you find interesting. Cookies are small text files that may remain on your computer's hard drive for a period of time that may be used to maintain data relevant to your navigation of the Internet, save personal settings and information, and track web browsing habits. Web beacons are clear picture files that you cannot see that we use to monitor traffic and track your activities on the Internet.

## HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

### We use this information in several ways:

  * to give you a more enjoyable, convenient shopping experience, learn about your habits, personalize your user experience, and help us identify and/or provide information, products or services that may be of interest to you;
  * to support and enhance your use of the Services and their features, including without limitation: fulfilling your order; providing customer service; tracking email invitations you send; and otherwise supporting your use of the Services and its features;
  * to conduct market research, improve the Services and help us identify others who may be interested in the Services;
  * to serve you ads tailored to your interests or to tailor ads that may be served to you when you visit other websites, mobile applications or social media networks; and
  * in other ways for which we provide specific notice at the time of collection.

We may share the information that you provide to us, and the information that we collect about you as described above, to others (including social media networks and advertising service providers and networks) to serve you ads tailored to your interests or to tailor ads that may be served to you on our website and mobile application, as well as other websites and mobile applications, and on social media networks. In some cases, this may involve transferring your personal information to parties located in other countries.

We may permit certain trusted third parties to access your information in connection with their performance of services to maintain and operate our websites and mobile applications and certain features on the Services. For example, we may use third parties to host the websites and mobile applications; operate various features of the Services; send emails; analyze data; provide search results and links and assist in fulfilling your orders.

From time to time, we may share your personally identifiable information in connection with strategic relationships. Some of these strategic relationships may include operating a co-branded website or web pages with a strategic partner. You should be aware that these co-branded sites may collect different or additional information. Additionally, we may provide links to websites controlled by third parties. We have no control over these websites and our privacy policy does not apply to these third party websites. Please consult the privacy policy of the website you are visiting.

Also, we may share personally identifiable or other information with our affiliates and across our various websites, apps and social media pages.

Occasionally, we provide our postal mailing list (consisting of customer names and postal mailing addresses, but not email addresses) to other companies for purposes of marketing the Services or other products or services that may be of interest to you. In order to determine the information that may be of interest to you, the information that you give us and information about your order may be combined with other personally identifiable information (such as demographic information and past purchase history) available from our records and other sources.

We may transfer personally identifiable information as an asset in connection with a proposed or actual merger or sale (including any transfers made as part of an insolvency or bankruptcy proceeding) involving all or part of our business or as part of a corporate reorganization, stock sale or other change in control.

We reserve the right to disclose information in order to comply with a subpoena, court order, administrative or governmental order, or any other requirement of law, or when we, in our sole discretion, believe it is necessary in order to protect our rights or the rights of others, to prevent harm to persons or property, to fight fraud and credit risk reduction.

If you use a bulletin board, chat room or any other publicly accessible area of our websites or mobile applications, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected or used by any person for any purpose. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable or other information you choose to submit in these forums.

We use non-personally identifiable information in the aggregate, so that we can improve our Services and for business and administrative purposes. We may also use or share with third parties for any purpose aggregated data that contains no personally identifiable information.

## CHOICE AND OPT-OUT

We offer you certain choices about the collection, use and sharing of your information:

Marketing Communications

\- You may choose not to receive marketing email communications from us by clicking on the unsubscribe link in the marketing emails. You may change your email address for receipt of such communications by going to My Account. You may choose to opt out of receiving marketing communications through our mobile app notifications and text notifications in the manner identified when you opt in to receive those notifications.

Location Data

\- When you use our mobile applications, you can choose not to share your location data by adjusting the applicable settings on your mobile device (the manufacturer or your service provider should be able to provide assistance).

Targeted Advertising

\- As noted above, we may use the information you provide to us, and information we collect about your use of our products and services, to assist us and our partners in our effort to deliver you online advertising that is relevant to your interests. In connection with these activities, we may work with social media networks and advertising service providers who help deliver these ads to you. These advertising service providers may also use cookies, web beacons and similar technologies to collect and track information such as demographic information, aggregated information, and Internet activity to assist them in delivering advertising that is more relevant to your interests.

If you do not wish to have us collect, use and share information about you to deliver targeted online advertising in this manner, email your request to customercare@italist.com. Please also note that most opt-out mechanisms are cookie-based and will only affect the specific computer and browser that is used to submit an opt-out request. If you have multiple computers or change computers, or use multiple browsers, you will need to submit opt-out requests for each such computer or browser. In addition, if you delete, block or otherwise restrict cookies, you will need to renew your opt-out choices to ensure that any opt-out cookies remain effective.

## ACCESSING AND UPDATING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION AND PREFERENCES

If you are a registered user, you may access and update your registration information and your preferences to receive email or other communications from us by sending an email to customercare@italist.com. We will take commercially reasonable steps to implement your opt-out requests promptly, but you may still receive communications from us for up to ten (10) business days as we process your request.

While we make efforts to accommodate requests to restrict our use of your information, we reserve the right to delete all or any portion of customer information if we are not able to reasonably accommodate a requested restriction.

## HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION

We are committed to protecting the information we receive from you. We follow reasonable technical and management practices to help protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of data stored on our system. While no computer system is completely secure, we believe the measures we have implemented reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved.

We encrypt your credit card number and other personal information using secure socket layer (SSL) or similarly secure technology to provide for the secure transmission of the information from your PC or device to our servers. In addition, only those employees and third parties who need access to your information in order to perform their duties are allowed such access.

We also require you to enter a password to access your account. We recommend that you not disclose your password to unauthorized people.

## CHILDREN’S PRIVACY AND PARENTAL CONTROLS

We do not solicit any personal information from children. If you are not 18 or older, you are not authorized to use the Services. Parents should be aware that there are parental control tools available online that you can use to prevent your children from submitting information online without parental permission or from accessing material that is harmful to minors.

## YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

If you are a California resident, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits you to request information regarding the disclosure of your personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to [customercare@italist.com](mailto:customercare%40italist.com) or write to us at the following address:

italist Inc.  
10350 Santa Monica Blvd.  
Suite 160  
Los Angeles, CA 90025

## PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES

If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will post the revised Privacy Policy here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we may disclose it to anyone. Your continued use of the Services indicates your consent to the Privacy Policy as posted.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

italist Inc.  
Diego Abba, CEO  
10350 Santa Monica Blvd.  
Suite 160  
Los Angeles, CA 90025  
Email: [legal@italist.com](mailto:legal%40italist.com)
